Art Collins Collection ARC.0001
Library and Archives
- Series I: Iggy Pop Legal Papers, 1995-2004 and undated
  - "Passenger" Mercedes Benz (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - "Lust for Life” Mitsubishi Mix CD (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - "Search and Destroy" The Life Aquatic (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Royal Caribbean (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Rugrats Go Wild Heir Letters (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - "The Passenger" 70 A L'heure (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - "Search and Destroy" Skate Video (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - "Search and Destroy" Wonderland (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - "Raw Power" Aloha Surf (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - "The Passenger" Tommy Hilfiger CD (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - "Lust for Life" 20th Century Masters (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Bourne Supremacy poster use (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - "The Passenger" Time Life Classic Vol. 1&4 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Royal Caribbean, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - "Lust for Life" LAS 101 Mejores (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Earthlink (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - "Lust for Life" Don Cherry's Hockey Hits (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - "Lust for Life" LA Republica (Italy) (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - "Search and Destroy" Haggard Skateboard Stunts (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - The Life Aquatic / licensing (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - "Lust for Life" Greenpeace (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - "Candy" 100% Rolling Stone (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - "Louie Louie" French perfume (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - "Nightclubbing" ringtone use (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Motor Inn Clubber's Guide (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - "I Wanna Be Your Dog" That 70's Show (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - "Lust for Life" Roxy Club and Rock (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Barney Hoskins book proposal (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - "Moonlight Lady" My Baby Wants to R&R (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - "The Passenger" Discoteque Ideal (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - "Candy" Play My Music (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - "Lust for Life" Modern Edge/Time Life (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - "Search and Destroy" The Wire HBO (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - "American Caesar" Brick by Brick (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Sick of You T-Shirt (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - "Lust for Life" Absolut Classics 2 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - "The Passenger" Insight Music / UK (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - "Lust for Life" Punk Hits (Malaysia) (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - "Lust for Life" Disky-Punk Classics (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - "Lust for Life" Nice-TV Hits and Pop (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - "American Caesar" Japan Mid Price (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - "No Fun" School Of Rock (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - "Idiot/Lust for Life" Box Set Offer (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - "Passenger" Gear One Sweden (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - "Lust for Life" Universal Music 70's Album (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Album information (Box 25, Folder 50-52)
  - "The Passenger" Festival Vieilles (France) (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - "Passenger/Lust" French single (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - "Private Hell" Glow (Japan) (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - "Lust for Life" Rockline #4 (France) (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - "Penetration" MasterCard (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - "Little Know it All" Nascar Thunder 2004 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - "Nightclubbing" Future, Past, Perfection (EMI Asia) (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - "Blood on Your Cool" Gran Turismo (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - "Little Electric" Anti-Grav Game (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - "The Passenger" Coors Brewing (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - "Search and Destroy" VW Touran SUV (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - "Louie Louie" Coffee and Cigarettes (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - "Lust for Life" World Cup Hockey (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Carroll Etc. Invoice, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Universal statement, April 2004 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Elektra statement, April 2004 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - "The Passenger" Lost in Translation (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Licensing requests, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - "TV Eye" Lords of Dogtown (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - "The Passenger" Autospot Italy (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - "Success" I Love the 90's (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - "China Girl" Canadian Idol (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - "Lust/Passenger/Nightclubbing" Gold 7 Platinum (BMG) (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - "Lust for Life" The District (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - "The Passenger" Polish Beer Co. (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - "MoonLight Lady" Minos (EMI Greece) (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - "Candy" Tabcorp Premium (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - The Skeleton Key / T-Shirt usage (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - "Lust for Life" declined usage (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - David McGee schedule (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - "Lust for Life" Best Beer CD (EMI Canada) (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - A&M Songs for EMI Box Set (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - "Lust for Life" Fernanda on the Rock (EMI Italy) (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - "Candy" Video (EMI Chile) (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - "Penetration" An Obsession (Short Film) (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - "Private Hell" Cracking Up (Fox Comedy) (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - "The Passenger" Coors Aspen Edge (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - "Whatever" Razzmatazz (Spain) (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - "Lust for Life" The Movie Show (Australia) (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - "The Passenger" Power Ballads (Portugal) (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - "The Passenger" Les Hits De La Pub (Portugal) (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Receipts, January 2003 to January 2004 (Box 26, Folder 42-47)
  - Mauro Deceglie / Virgin product management (Box 26, Folder 48-50)
  - Virgin press (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - Simone De Vries / Being Iggy (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - Virgin International promo requests (Box 26, Folder 53)
  - Jean Marc Foliet / Iggy recording proposal (Box 26, Folder 54)
  - Zombie Birdhouse / New Millennium proposal (Box 26, Folder 55)
  - Royalties reunited (Box 26, Folder 56)
  - Anthill (Box 26, Folder 57-58)
  - Brigitte Fontaine / French singer (Box 26, Folder 59)
  - Licensing contracts (Box 26, Folder 60)
  - Solo Japan (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Bad Boys Special Delivery (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Coachella gig (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Y100 Philly sessions (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - "The Passenger" The Weather Man (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - "Loose" Lords of Dogtown (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Royal Caribbean (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - "Lust for Life" The Simpsons (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - "I'm Bored" VH1 Totally Obsessed (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - "The Passenger" Drew Barrymore Voting Documentary (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - "Success" and "Lust for Life" Ski Video (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - "The Passenger" I love TV Ads (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - "Lust for Life" Veronica Mars (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - "Boogie Boy" Crossing Jordan (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - "Lust for Life" Royal Caribbean (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - "Motor Inn" Virgin Dance (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - "I Wanna be Your Dog" Friday Night Lights (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - "Lust for Life" Pure Punk (Malaysia) (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - "The Passenger" Pure Punk (Malaysia) (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - David Bowie Reality Tour (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - "Little Know it All" Summerland TV Show (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - "The Passenger" 50 Anni de Rock (Italy) (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - "I'll Be Seeing You" Coffee Company (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - "The Passenger" Rock TV Classics (Italy) (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - "TV Eye" Nissan Xterra (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Iggy pop / Deryck Whibley Contract (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - "Motor Inn" Dance Star, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - "Whatever" Razzamatazz, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - "Lust for Life" Radio Two (Holland) (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - "Lust for Life" Border's Rock Essentials Vol. 3 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - "The Passenger" Lost in Translation (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - "Lust for Life" Royal Caribbean Web Site Use (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Lou Reed / Kansas City Project (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Bug statements (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Bug licensing (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - "Gimme Danger" The Life Aquatic (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Grumble Corporation / Foreign insurance (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - South Bank show (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Shure Microphones (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Anita Gelman settlement (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Mike McCarthy, Memphis film maker (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Europe promo (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Licensing (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Anthill trading (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Mauro Deceglie / Virgin general (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Soundscan reports (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Steve Smith / S&D screenplay (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Hunt sales (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Floyd statements (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Skull Ring / Soundscan (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Fat Possum contract (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Elextra Nissan / TV eye (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - David Brady advertising (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Virgin Radio promotion (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - "Search and Destroy" Volkswagen Touran (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - "Candy" Con Nombre De Mujer (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - "Little Know It All" Summerland (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - "The Passenger” The Weatherman Film (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - 1969 Dick Rude's/Joe Strummer (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Alejandro Escoverdo (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Coffee and Cigarettes / United Artists Film (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - "Hellhounds" Poochwear (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - David Bowie book (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Funhouse art show (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Greece Olympics (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Virgin Radio promotion (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - "Lust for Life" Comedy Central (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - "Thumbsucker" I'm Alright (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Anita Gelman contract (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - "The Passenger" Spanish Phones (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - "Shake Appeal" LaCoste State of Liberty Fund (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - "Lust for Life" The Billionaire (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - "The Passenger" Lust - Ultimate Rock (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Elektra statement / Janine letter (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Elektra statement, September 2003 (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - "The Passenger" Expedition Outreach (Austria) (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - "Lust for Life" EMI Rock Box (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Bowie: Reality tour (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - Ricky Gardner / Bug mention (Box 28, Folder 46)
  - Verizon Wireless voice over’s (Box 28, Folder 47)
  - Fat Possum Jr. tribute (Box 28, Folder 48)
  - "China Girl" The Sopranos (HBO) (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - “Dog” Rock Heroes Live (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - "Dog" VH1 Top 100 Artists (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - "Fell in Love With Me/Lust for Life" Stupid Kids Off BTW (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - "Lust for Life" licensing (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - "Moonlight Lady" Heavy in Love (EMI Spain) (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - "Nightclubbing" Banana Republic (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - "Nightclubbing" Virgin France (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - "The Passenger" licensing (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - "Private Hell" Glow (Toshiba EMI) (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - "Wild American" South Bank TV (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - "Winners and Losers" Miami Vice home video (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - A Day in the Garden (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Aaron Jacoves (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Doctor Music festival (Spain) (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Front Page Merch magazine covers (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Graz date (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Highland festival (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Hurricane festival (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Jim and Suchi agreement (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - July German date (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - MS 45 / Talent House (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Natalie Jacobson information (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Norway gig (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Phillippe Dubreuille (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Rock Show Winter Games (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Roskilde (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Royal Caribbean (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Siemens (Germany) (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Sweetwater’s (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Swiss gig (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - The Wedding Singer / BUG music (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Twentieth Grammy Awards program (Box 29, Folder 33)
- Series II: Iggy Pop Clippings, 1986-1999 and undated
  Contains newspapers, periodicals, and loose clippings relating to Iggy Pop’s album releases and tour information. The files are arranges chronologically.
  - Shoreline Music Festival production directory (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Instinct press (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - A&M press (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Canada press (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Tourstar (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Nice Man merchandising (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Brockum (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Creative Artists Agency / Pretenders (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Europe tour, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Tour insurance (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Europe tour, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Japan tour, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Pretenders tour (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - UK Tour – merchandise, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Tour budget/income, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Status reports (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - USA tour, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Sales figures (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Expenses (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Tour data (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Contracts (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Grammy's file (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Various photos (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - JLM information (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - USA tour, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - A&M records (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - "Isolation" video (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - "Cry for Love" video (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Recording information (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - "Cry for Love" information (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - "Cry Baby" information (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Charts and sales figures (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Bug Music royalties and figures (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Credits (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - New album information (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - South America tour, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Tour rider, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Relativity record distribution (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - AEI / Linda Hilton (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - Sakamoto attorney information (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - Steve Jones release (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - Alfred Knopf contract (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - A&M contract (Box 30, Folder 43)
  - Westwood 1 contract (Box 30, Folder 44)
  - Press information (Box 30, Folder 45)
  - Agreement and contract (Box 30, Folder 46)
  - Latin America Tour, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 47)
  - Press, July 1987 (Box 30, Folder 48)
  - Band Per Diam receipts (Box 30, Folder 49)
  - Producer / IP agreement "Instinct" (Box 30, Folder 50)
  - "Instinct" album credits (Box 30, Folder 51)
  - Studio information (Box 30, Folder 52)
  - Recording schedule (Box 30, Folder 53)
  - American Federation of Musicians contract information (Box 30, Folder 54)
  - International press (Box 30, Folder 55)
  - JLM Management press (Box 30, Folder 56)
  - Budget information (Box 30, Folder 57)
  - Bug music (Box 30, Folder 58)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 30, Folder 59)
  - Band members (Box 30, Folder 60)
  - David Donahue documentary (Box 30, Folder 61)
  - Financial receipts (Box 30, Folder 62)
  - JLM Management bills (Box 30, Folder 63)
  - Public Relations status report, January to June 1986 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Public Relations status report, July to December 1986 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Foreign press, miscellaneous articles, and magazines (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - A&M "Blah,Blah,Blah", 1986 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Press photos, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous articles, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous articles, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous articles, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous articles, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 9-12)
  - Iggy Pop and Henry Rollins photo (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous newspaper articles, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous newspaper articles, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Tour contracts, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 2-7)
  - Magazine articles, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous newspaper articles, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Foreign promo (Box 32, Folder 10-12)
  - Promo (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - William Morris agency contracts, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 1-4)
  - Iggy Pop photographs, 1987-1988 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Avenue B live reviews, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - I Need More by Iggy Pop (3 copies) (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous articles, 1990-1999 (Box 33, Folder 8-11)
- Series III: Iggy Pop Correspondence, 1998-1999 and undated
  Contains letters from fans to Iggy Pop. Most of the envelopes are unopened. The files are arranged chronologically by postmark.
  - Fan mail, mostly unopened, 1998 (Box 34)
  - Iggy Pop letter to Guns and Roses (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Fan mail, mostly unopened, 1999 (Box 35)
- Series IV: Marianne Faithful Legal Papers, 1992-1997 and undated
  Contains documents relating to Faithful’s Secret Life album and tour. This includes contracts, correspondence, tour information, album, and licensing information. The files are arranged chronologically.
  - Press information (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - TV documentaries (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - New album (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Studio budget (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Bertrand Lamblot correspondence (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Lyrics (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Movie requests (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - EMI International CD-ROM Request (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - City of Lost Children (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Island Spoken Word (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Under the Influence (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Blazing Away Inc. (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Lighting companies (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Anna LaCasio correspondence (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Chris Connelly correspondence (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Alahondro Escovedo correspondence (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - General information (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Martin Baker MF documentary (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Miami Light project (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Dutch Radio, Kurt Weill (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - "Pigs Fly" Review (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Contract (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - First Avenue gig cost (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - 20th Century Pop (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - MF letters of complaint (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Roberto Mann correspondence (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Robbins Speilman correspondence (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - APLA concert (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Touring (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Bios (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Set list (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Publishing (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Island licenses (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Angelo correspondence (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Passport information (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Montreaux Jazz Festival (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Radio press (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - Talent agency contracts (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - Ian Coombes correspondence (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Cultural Industry, 7 Deadly proposal (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Claudie Ossard correspondence (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Outstanding Island press requests (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - JT Lewis Vienna correspondence (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Band information and equipment (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Royalties (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Tracking (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Producer contract (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - RZO - Lust for Life (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Tour budget and final (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Island address change (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Bill Wyman / Sticky Fingers (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Squeeze Comp. LP (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Arthur Cantor correspondence (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Hillary Bratton correspondence (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Ogilvy and Mather correspondence (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Brian Jones movie (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Mick Jagger correspondence (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Time Warner cable (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Ian Coombes correspondence (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Australia information (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Barney's clothes (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - APLA Aids (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - American Airlines (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Dr. Tam correspondence (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Crossing Border festival (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Weiman cabaret (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - European tour (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Oxford union (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - 7 Deadly Sins (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - Solo contract (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - Promotions (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Marketing (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Bios (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - International (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - Photos (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - Video production (Box 37, Folder 38)
- Series V: Art Collins Personal Files, 2000-2005 and undated
  Contains files relating to Collins’ personal life, including correspondence, tax information, invoices, orders, travel information, and family information. The files are arranged chronologically.
  - Orders in progress (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Stuff for the curious (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Travis Mcgee (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Biography (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Photographs (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Mexican retirement ideas (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Mailing Information (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Financial records (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Licensing information (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Tour schedules (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - EMI DVD & Box Set (Box 38, Folder 11-13)
  - E-mail correspondence (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Band documents (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Virgin license agreement (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Music Video distributors (Box 38, Folder 17-18)
  - Musicologist report (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Bug Music report (Box 38, Folder 20)
- Series VI: John Lennon Printed Materials, Bulk, 1980-1981; 1964-1995
  Divided into two subseries: periodicals and newspapers. Both subseries contain articles relating to John Lennon’s life and death. The files are arranged alphabetically within the subseries and then chronologically.
  - Subseries 1: Periodicals
    - Life Magazine, 1964 January 31 (Box 39, Object 1)
    - Life Magazine, 1969 July 18 (Box 39, Object 2)
    - Life Magazine, 1969 August 29 (Box 39, Object 3)
    - Life Magazine, 1969 September 5 (Box 39, Object 4)
    - Life Magazine, 1969 October 31 (Box 39, Object 5)
    - Life Magazine, 1969 November 7 (Box 39, Object 6)
    - Life Magazine, 1969 December 19 (Box 39, Object 7)
    - Life Magazine, 1971 April 16 (Box 39, Object 8)
    - Life Magazine, 1989 August (Box 39, Object 9)
    - Life Magazine, 1995 December 11 (Box 39, Object 10)
    - National Enquirer, 1977 September 6 (Box 39, Object 11)
    - National Enquirer, 1980 December 30 (Box 39, Object 12)
    - New Musical Express, 1980 December 13 (Box 39, Object 13)
    - New Musical Express, 1981 June 27 (Box 39, Object 14)
    - The New Paper, 1980 December 10 (Box 39, Object 15)
    - New York Magazine, 1981 June 22 (Box 39, Object 16)
    - Record World, 1980 December 20 (Box 39, Object 17)
    - Soho News, 1980 December 3 (Box 39, Object 18)
  - Subseries 2: Newspapers
    - Daily News Tonight, 1981 March 9 (Box 40, Object 1)
    - New Musical Express, 1981 July (Box 40, Object 2)
    - New York Post, 1979 July 27 (Box 40, Object 3)
    - New York Post, 1980 December 10 (Box 40, Object 4)
    - New York Post, 1980 December 11 (Box 40, Object 5)
    - New York Post, 1980 December 12 (Box 40, Object 6)
    - New York Post, 1980 December 13 (Box 40, Object 7)
    - New York Post, 1980 December 15 (Box 40, Object 8)
    - New York Post, 1980 December 16 (Box 40, Object 9)
    - New York Post, 1980 December 30 (Box 40, Object 10)
    - New York Post, 1981 February 9 (Box 40, Object 11)
    - New York Post, 1981 February 17 (Box 40, Object 12)
    - New York Post, 1981 March 22 (Box 40, Object 13)
    - New York Post, 1981 June 11 (Box 40, Object 14)
    - New York Post, 1981 June 22 (Box 40, Object 15)
    - New York Post, 1981 June 23 (Box 40, Object 16)
    - New York Post, 1981 June 24 (Box 40, Object 17)
    - New York Post, 1981 July 9 (Box 40, Object 18)
    - New York Post, 1981 July 10 (Box 40, Object 19)
    - New York Post, 1981 September 18 (Box 40, Object 20)
    - The New York Times, 1980 December 10 (Box 40, Object 21)
    - The New York Times, 1980 December 11 (Box 40, Object 22)
    - The New York Times, 1980 December 14 (Box 40, Object 23)
    - The New York Times, 1981 January 18 (Box 40, Object 24)
    - Radio and Records, 1980 December 14 (Box 40, Object 25)
    - Soho News, 1980 December 10 (Box 40, Object 26)
    - The Village Voice, 1980 December 10 (Box 40, Object 27)
- Series VII: Audiovisual Materials [RESTRICTED], 1966-2005 and undated
  Separated Materials
  DVDs and 45 RPM records have been transferred to the library collection. Please search for the "Art Collins Papers" in the library catalog for a list of donated titles.
  Access Restrictions